♪ [bongo beats] ♪.
(Leonard)
Don’t let this be Sheldon playing bongos.
Please don’t let this be Sheldon playing bongos.
(Sheldon)
♪ Hello Leonard, do you like my bongos?
♪ Bet you didn’t know that I had bongos? ♪
(Leonard)
Sheldon it’s 3 o’clock in the morning.
(Sheldon)
♪ 3:00 in the morning is a good time for bongos. ♪
(Leonard)
I was sleeping.
(Sheldon)
♪ Leonard sleeps while I play bongos. ♪
(Leonard)
No he doesn’t.
(Sheldon)
♪ Leonard no sleep, while I pay bongos, bongo solo. ♪
(Leonard)
Stop, stop it.
[Sheldon plays bongo] (Penny)
What the hell?
(Leonard)
Oh hi Penny.  Guess what, Sheldon got bongos.
(Penny)
Why did you get bongos?
(Sheldon)
Richard Feynman played the bongos, I thought I give that a  try.
(Leonard)
Richard Feynman was a famous physicist.
(Penny)
Leonard it’s 3 o’clock in the morning.
I don’t care if Richard Feynman was a purple leprechaun who lived in my  butt.
(Sheldon)
♪ Penny meant if he were a purple leprechaun. ♪
♪ Penny forgot to use the subjunctive. ♪
(Leonard)
Sheldon go to bed, you have work in the morning.
(Sheldon)
♪ Maybe, maybe not.   Maybe tomorrow I start a bongo band and tour the world.
(Leonard)
No hang on roommate agreement.
No hootenanny, sing-alongs or barbershop quartets after 10 PM.
(Sheldon)
Roommate agreement, are you kidding?  We are living in a world of chaos.  Roommate agreement.
(Penny)
Where are you going?
(Sheldon)
Wherever the music takes me kitten.
♪ I play bongo walking down the stairs. ♪
[thud] Oh. ♪ Never play bongo walking down the stairs ♪.